<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Essteling games</string>
    <string name="scan">SCAN</string>
    <string name="title_text">Minigames</string>
    <string name="minigamename_placeholder">minigame name placeholder</string>
    <string name="attempts_placeholder">attempts placeholder</string>
    <string name="StartButton">Start</string>
    <string name="CancelButton">Cancel</string>
    <string name="PopUpText">Welcome to the Essteling games. Games that can be played after riding an attraction. If you want to play, press the start button and choose a character in the following screen. Afterwards you can begin playing an assortiment of minigames and compete with others in The Essteling. Good luck!</string>
    <string name="minigame_introduction">minigame Introduction</string>
    <string name="animal_name">animal name</string>
    <string name="choose_your_character">Choose your character!</string>
    <string name="DroomReisInformation">In the Droomreid attraction, the visitor goes on a journey through unknown worlds full of exotic plants and animals. You fly around in a zeppelin through the landscape, sometimes up, sometimes down, sometimes faster, sometimes harder, and you end up on a grass field in a beautiful gliding flight. All senses are addressed: feeling, seeing, hearing and smelling. That’s why this attraction is also very suitable for people with disabilities. </string>
    <string name="ZwevendeBelgInformation">De Zwevende Belg is a combination of a walk area, a wattercoaster and a ‘darkride’ with boats. It’s located in the Stoerland part of the Essteling</string>
    <string name="JohanInformation">Johan en de Eenhoorn is a wooden racing-rollercoaster, build around the legend of Saint Johan and the Unicorn. Is your rollercoaster ride faster than the opponent? Do you know how to overtake and catch the Unicorn? Experience it!</string>
    <string name="CobraInformation">The Cobra is a classic rollercoaster which was once the first steal rollercoaster in the Essteling. It is still populair because of its speed and loopings</string>
    <string name="qr_explanation">Show this QR-code to one of our employees to redeem your price!</string>
    <string name="play">PLAY!</string>
</resources>
